Are you nervous?
緊張してる?
Why are you nervous?
なんで緊張してるの?
After we had sex?
エ ッチした後だから?
After having sex?
エッチした後だから?
Wait a minute, we had sex earlier.
ちょっとね、さっきね エッチしちゃったからね
how was it?
どう だった?
Ah, it was so cute that I did it.
あ、クッと 可愛すぎて やっちゃいました
Cute kimono. I like this one. It's recent.
可愛 いなもん、着物 いいね、このもんっていうことね 最近め
I'll take a look at it, but what?
っちゃ 見るんだけど なに?
You're wearing so much clothes that I want to look at the flowers. Oh, that's right.
すごい着てんの 花見たいくらい あ そうだよね
I'm looking at it a lot, but...
め っちゃ見るんだけど さあ、なんか
What do you usually do?
普 段は なにしてるの?
Women's college, right?
女子大 そうなの?
Women's college?
女子大?
There are only girls. Oh, by the way, how big is it?
女子しかいない あら ちなみにどこ大なの?
Are you a tea drinker?
お茶飲み は?
Tea drinker, why are you supposed to be so smart? You're such an idiot.
お茶飲み なんでそんな 頭いいはずなのに すごいバカ バカ
You say it like that, you're smart, right?
っぽ く言うね 賢いんでしょ あ、
Is that so? No boys?
そうなんだ 男子ない?
I want to go home. Can I go home?
帰りたい 帰っていい?
Is it okay?
いいの?
Yes, do you have a boyfriend?
はい 彼氏いいの?
No, I'm recruiting. How many people have you dated so far?
いないね 募集中 今まで何人と付き合ったことあるの?
Oh, alone?
あ、一人?
when?
いつ?
By the way, how many people have experience?
ちなみに経験人数とか 何人くらい?
Alone, oh, alone, amazing
一人 あ、一人 すごい
High school?
高 校の?
boyfriend?
彼氏?
Okay, only one person has done it, but how many times has it happened?
いいな 一人しかしてない でも何回ました?
Oh, he seemed to like it.
あ ら 好きそうだった
She had such an erotic body. Wouldn't she go out with anyone other than her boyfriend?
すごい エロい体してた 彼氏以外でうちしない?
Why don't you do it? It's a women's university, so I'm doing part-time videos.
しないか 女子大だし バイト動画してます?
Welcome, welcome, welcome.
いらっしゃいませ いらっしゃいませ いらっしゃいませ だいた
Welcome
い いらっしゃいませ
Where are you, Miss Don? Miss Don?
ど このいらっしゃいませ ミス丼です ミス丼?
I'm sure you're welcome, Miss Don. I've been wanting to eat something lately, haven't I?
確かに いらっしゃいませ ミス丼最近何か 食べたいんだよね
no chu apple
の っちゅうりんご
It'll probably sell out soon. I'll buy it when I see it.
す ぐ売り切れるんだろ じ ゅうじと みずになられば 買え
I can't buy it, so I'll think about it. Make it. It's impossible.
ます 買えないんだよ ならんでも 考えます 作ってよ 無理ね
I'm begging you. Only the cash register is out. I haven't made anything.
頼 むよ レジしか出てない 作ってない
I just took a breath
さ っき息したから
This bottom,
この 下がさ、
base.
ベ ース
I was also doing spatula earlier.
さっきさ、ヘラもしてる
Right?
で しょ?
Because I don't have many opportunities to interact with boys.
あんまり男子と接する機会がないから
Ignore?
無視する?
Ah, yes.
あ、そう
You do a really cool job.
めっちゃかっこいい仕事をするじゃ
yeah.
ん
Hmm.
う ーん
Follow me, this is it.
ついてくね、これね
It depends on the person, I guess.
人によるよね、そんなのね
Ah, that's right.
あ、 そうだ
Is there one?
あるんだっけ?
Isn't that what it is?
なんか、あれじゃない?
Are you a man?
男れ?
mosquito
か
Well, it was.
ん そうでしたけど
That's right, it's a kimono.
そうだよね、着物だもん
hey.
ね
Men have sex, the future is
男 の人はエッチしてさ、未来は
difference.
さ
So, over a year?
じゃあ、 1年以上とか?
1 person.
1人です
Because of that,
そういうので、
That's right.
そうだ よね
ERROR
有名なのかな?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
It's black, even the bottom.
黒だね、下も
There are a lot of black ones
黒が多いも
yeah.
ん
I was brought here.
連 れてこられた
Brought to me.
俺に連れてこられた
There are a lot here, though.
ここ多いよ、でも
Was it beautiful?
きれいだった?
Did you see it locally?
現地で見たの?
That's right.
だよね
Are there too many people?
人多すぎない?
ERROR
遠くのビルから
Was it found in a building far away?
遠くのビルから見つかった?
It was found at the top of the building.
ビルの奥上から見つかった
Is it a little far away?
ちょっと離れたところかな?
It's thin in the back.
後ろで薄いね
I did it myself.
自分でやった
It's white, it's skin.
白いね、肌ね
There are a lot of these.
いっぱいあるね、これ
This is one of many patterns.
いっぱいあるパターンのやつだ、これ
This is terrible.
やばい、これ
Let's wash it with shame.
恥ずかしながら洗おう
Can you show me?
見せてくれる?
It sunk.
沈んだわ
I was just jumping up and down.
さっき飛び跳ねてたよ
I caught it.
釣れました
May I see it?
見せていただいてもいいですか?
I get closer.
近づいてしまう
river
かわ
good.
いい
what happened?
どう したの?
happy?
うれしい?
It tastes like lavender.
ラベンダーの味がする
What do you mean?
どういう事?
Do you feel tingly?
チクビ感じるの?
Are you sensitive?
敏感なの?
Do you touch it yourself?
自分で触ったりする?
a little bit?
ちょっと?
By yourself?
自 分で?
I don't feel any tingling at all.
チクビが全然感じない
Is it new?
新しいの?
Mumble exchange.
ブツブツ交換
Uniform exchange.
ユニフォーム交換
You have a beautiful body.
綺麗な体してるね
The bus looks super cool.
バスが超カッコよくしてる
Just your own amount.
自分の量でさ
You look at it a lot, right?
めっちゃ見るでしょ?
what happened?
どうしたの?
I'm really surprised.
すごいビックリするね
You're sensitive.
敏感だね
My clitoris is sensitive.
クリが敏感なの
Have you ever been licked?
舐められたことあるでしょ?
amazing.
すごい
Something came out
何か出てきた
hey.
ね
Your butt is wet.
お 尻が濡れちゃってるね
You have a nice ass.
良いケツしてるな
My whole body is sensitive though.
全身敏感なんだけど
What are you most sensitive to?
どうが一番敏感なんだ?
all.
全部
all?
全部?
all.
全部
Stick it on top of the penta.
ペンタの上に刺す
The way you touch me is erotic, isn't it?
触り方がエロいよね
That's crazy, the way you touch it.
やばいね、触り方が
This is a little crazy.
これはちょっとヤバいわ
I'm crazy.
ヘロヘロしてる
here
ここ
but...
が...
Let it out, let it out.
出して、出して
Please raise your feet well.
足をよく掲げてください
I'm going.
行っちゃうよ
Can I take it out?
出していい?
amazing.
すごい
You did it.
やっちゃったね
You're exhausted, aren't you?
くたくたでしょ
I'm here again, Yukata.
また 来ちゃったんだ、浴衣
Wow, that's it.
すごい、あれだね
Let's go in.
入ろうな
There's a lot of stuff coming out.
出してばっかりある
Even though I just put it out.
出してばっかりなのに
Even though it's big magma.
ビッグマグマなのに
What should I do?
どうしよう?
Is it big magma?
ビッグマグマなの?
Big mug?
ビッグマグ?
Is there something like a technician?
テクニシャンみたいなやつある?
technician?
テクニシャン?
That's amazing.
すごいね
Move a little slower.
ちょっとゆっくり動いて
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
amazing
すごい
hey.
ね
Please look here.
こ っちを見てください
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Oh my goodness.
や ばいね
air
気
Is it small?
持 ちいい?
Yeah?
うん?
or
や
times.
ばい
Raise your upper body.
上 半身が起こしてさ
It doesn't seem like it will come out.
出なさそう
I put it out again.
また出しちゃったよ
By yourself.
自分で
I thought this was great.
こういいなと思って
Hey.
ねえ
a little bit.
ちょっと
nice.
いいね
picture?
え?
It's been a long time since I came here.
久々に来たんだ
As for underwear.
下着は
a little bit.
ちょっと
Just a little bit.
ちょっとね
It's like this.
こうなってる
It feels like you can see it.
見えちゃう感じでしょ
It's like wearing a hot spring outfit.
温泉着てるみたいな
Good.
よいしょ
Huh?
あれ?
just,
ただ、
It's beautiful.
き れいだね
Back.
背中って
My legs are like this.
足がこう
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいね
It's sinking.
沈むね
I'm going to sink into bed.
ベッドに沈んでいっちゃうね
It's going to sink.
沈むよね
It's inside like this.
こんな中がさ
So that I can see it.
見えるようにさ
With both hands.
両手でさ
I saw it up close.
間近で見ちゃいました
Hey.
ね え
Show me some more.
もうちょい見せて
You've never seen it before.
見したことないでしょ
Hey.
ねえ
here
ここ
Is it okay?
いい の?
at close distance
しきん距離に
hey.
ね
It feels good though.
気 持ちいいんだけど
A good touch.
上手な触り方
See you then.
じゃあさ
That's amazing.
すっごいなんか
The atmosphere is strong.
大気がさ
It's like lotion.
ローションみたい
It's an atmospheric lotion.
大気ローションだね
Can I just say it like this?
このまま口に出していい?
good?
いい?
terrible.
やばい
You're really good at it.
すごい上手だね
I put out a lot.
いっぱい出しちゃったよ
What does it taste like?
どんな味する?
delicious?
おいしい?
I forgot to mention it.
言い忘れてるけど